https://www.taylorsecurity.com/service/privacy/

Skip to Main Content
Locks Interior DoorsExterior DoorsCommercial LocksPushbutton LocksStorefrontHome TechnologyCabinet & DrawerDecorative CabinetSliding DoorsCylindersKeyblanksLatches & Strikes Door Handles KnobsLeversDeadboltsHandlesetsSideplatesInterior PacksCommercial LocksPushbutton LocksMortise LocksKeying Kits & PinsCylindersKeyblanks Padlocks KeyedCombinationLockerStorageHasps & Hasp LocksCable & ChainSafety / LockoutBike & AutoCommercial / Government Institutional Pushbutton LocksElectric StrikesCDX-10 / X-10 / LKM10KDoor MagnetsDoor ClosersCommercial LocksExit DevicesAccess ControlCommercial PadlocksKey MachinesLocksmith ToolsKeyblanks Access Control Electric StrikesCDX-10 / X-10 / LKM10KPushbutton LocksDoor MagnetsKeypadsButtons & SwitchesPower TransferDoor ClosersExit DevicesKey MachinesLocksmith ToolsKeying Kits Door Hardware HingesSliding DoorsLatches & StrikesDoor Plates & WrapsDoor Stops & BoltsDoor Hooks & CatchesPivots & HoldersDoor Guards & PullsKeying Kits & PinsKeyblanksCylindersMore Door Hardware
Home>Customer Service
Credit Application
Line Card
Return Form
FAQ
Contact Us
Request a Quote
Credit Card Authorization Form
Privacy Policy
Taylor Security & Lock, a Craftmaster Hardware Company (Taylor), Privacy Policy:
By accessing or using the taylorsecurity.com Web site ("Site"), you agree to the terms of the Taylor Online Privacy Policy, as outlined below. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this Site. Taylor reserves the right to change the Online Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion.
1. Personal Information.
When you engage in certain activities on this site, such as ordering or registering products, Taylor may ask you to provide certain information by filling out and submitting an online form. These activities are optional. If you engage in these activities, Taylor may ask that you provide us personal information, such as your first and last name, mailing address (including zip code), e-mail address, employer, job title and department, telephone and facsimile numbers, and other personal identifying information. When ordering products or services on the site, you may be asked to provide a credit card number. Depending upon the activity, some of the information that we ask you to provide is identified as required. If you do not provide the required data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity.
2. Protection of Personal Information.
This Site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information submitted in connection with purchases made through the Site. Our secure server software (SSL) is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure commerce transactions. It encrypts all of your personal information, including credit card number, name, and address, so that it cannot be read as the information travels over the Internet.
The personal information that you provide in connection with participating in a Taylor forum is protected by a password and unique customer ID selected by you. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. Any information that you post to a public bulletin board or chat room, such as a Taylor Security forum, is available to all persons accessing that area of the Site and Taylor has no control over their use or further dissemination of such information.
3. Your IP Address.
Taylor may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with its server, and to administer the Site. Your IP address may be used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information about you.
4. Use of Information.
Taylor uses your information to record and support your participation in the activities you select to participate in through the Site. If you order a product or service through the Site, the information may be used to fulfill the product or service order. If you enter a contest, information may be used to qualify the entry and contact you regarding the contest and any awards. The information that you provide also may be used to keep you informed about product upgrades, special offers, and other products and services of Taylor and selected third parties. If third parties are involved in fulfilling product or service orders, information may be disclosed to them to enable fulfillment.
Taylor may use demographic information collected through the Site to adapt the Site to the interests of users visiting the Site. This information may be shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis so that advertisements on the Site may be directed to the appropriate audience.
5. Use of Cookies.
A cookie is small amount of data that is transferred to your browser by a Web server that can be read only by the server that gave it to you. It serves to identify your computer to the Web server and can be used to record passwords, purchases, and preferences. It cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses. The Site presently does not use cookies, but may in the future use them.
Most browser software initially is set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. However, some Web pages that require access authorization may operate only if cookies are accepted. Users choosing not to accept cookies probably will not be able to access those pages.
6. Trans-Border Transmissions.
When you submit personal information to Taylor on this Site, you understand and agree that this information may be transferred across national boundaries and may be stored and processed in any of the countries in which Taylor Security maintains offices, including without limitation, the United States. You also acknowledge that in certain countries or with respect to certain activities, the collection, transferring, storage and processing of your information may be undertaken by trusted vendors of Taylor.
7. Other Sites, Other Vendors and their Privacy Policies.
This Site may contain links to other Web sites. Taylor Security is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites or for the privacy policies and practices of third parties.
close (X)
